and this is the new pack of Charlie Brown Junior guy
and there broken in
now i come inland
I am with the PC my partner Charlie Brown
thanks hitchhike brother
I'm out of my mind,
don't you,
dad has to abuse his partner too
for that why do you roll with my chevas
it's also promised
already huh
if it works huh
caraca lie guys you're not on
we have news
for you i will show you first show the production
already running
call it bro
hand is screaming please
come on come on
and
this is the new pack from Charlie Brown Junior
here the sea break
here Brown
skateboard wheel format
touch pink original taste pink
typography
made by Tagus who was the artist
Charlie Brown Junior
and here comes the nutritional table already comes with
explain a little more there brother
here ó it's already coming with the ingredients
manufacturing lot
validity
there's everything back there guy alone
just coming brother
caraca brother tamo together
Charlie Brown and okay brother come on put here ó
that makes business happen
I really believe that this brand
can reach shelves and supermarkets
now with New branding here also nutritional table
what do you call this thing barcode
it's on doidão
all of the outfit
and then lie bro
and there ah
you're fine you're great guy showing the news
here from Charlie Brown
ame bro i wanted to tell you just fine
that I'm calling you
I see the noise that the parade is making
guy we talked
way over there at first and I think
on account of
accelerates that I'm giving
with bdv and these things i'm opening
I think it makes sense to us
talk if it makes sense
so i wait for you week at the office
delayed brother I will arrive can you rest assured
it's us hug tamo together valeu valeu
until tomorrow